gksolve.com 2018-05-10

# Privacy Policy - GK SOLVE read daily anywhere ,anytime

**_What information do we collect?_**  
**_  
_****_We collect information from you when you, comment the blog post and subscriber my blog post via email.You may however visit our my anonymously._**  
**_  
_****_What do my blog use your information for?_**  
**_  
_****_1\. For your experience ( Your information help me to better respond to your needs._**  
**_2\. To improve my site._**  
**_  
_****_Cookies: Yes, this blog is use cookies to remember your data when you make comment on blog post. this cookies are for visitor convencienc and purely optional._**  
**_  
_****_Google as third -party vendor, use cookies to serve ads on your site. Google uses of the DART cookies enables its to serve ads to your user based on thair visit to your sites and other site on internet.Users may opt out of the use the DART cookies by visiting the google ad and content network privacy policy._**  
**_  
_****_How do we protect your information?_**  
**_  
_****_We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety  of your personal information when you enter, submit and acesses your personal information._**  
**_  
_****_Online privacy policy only_**  
**_  
_****_This online privacy policy apllies only to informatoin collected through my blog and not to information collected offline._**  
**_  
_****_NOTE: this policy is subject to change anyitme at my sole discretion._**  
**_  
_****_Contacting Us:_**  
**_If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below._**  
**_jksolve.blogspot.com_**  
**_Canning, West Bengal,743329, India_**  
**_Contact no.-+ 91-9775878183_**

**_Email; swadeshgayen@gmail.com_**
